{
    "title": "Food Facts",
    "category": "food",
    "questions": [{
        "question": "Selling for as much as $600 a pound, where does the most expensive coffee in the world come from?",
        "choices": ["Hawaii",
        "sulfuric hot springs",
        "civet poop",
        "sparrow vomit"],
        "answer":2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which meat is traditionally seasoned with rosemary?",
        "choices": ["beef",
        "lamb",
        "pork",
        "turkey"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Around which river is Port wine traditionally produced",
        "choices": ["Douro",
        "Ebro",
        "Garonne",
        "Tagus"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is chorizo",
        "choices": ["Greek Dessert",
        "Italian Cheese",
        "Mexican Chicken",
        "Spanish Sausage"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "By what name do we normally refer to the Chinese Gooseberry?",
        "choices": ["Kiwi Fruit",
        "Mango",
        "Passion Fruit",
        "Star Fruit"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "From what fruit is Calvados distilled?",
        "choices": ["Grapes",
        "Apples",
        "Peaches",
        "Pears"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "From what is Welsh Laver bread made?",
        "choices": ["Leeks",
        "Lettuce",
        "Seaweed",
        "Spinach"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which herb comes from the dries stigmas of crocus flowers?",
        "choices": ["Saffron",
        "Cinnamon",
        "Paprika",
        "Turmeric"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the Merlot wine grape originally used?",
        "choices": ["Alsace",
        "Bordeaux",
        "Burgundy",
        "Loire"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In jam-making what is added to fruit to help them to set?",
        "choices": ["Arrowroot",
        "Lemon Juice",
        "Corn flour",
        "Gelatin"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which herb is used to make Pesto?",
        "choices": ["Dill",
        "Basil",
        "Mint",
        "Tarragon"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Halloumi?",
        "choices": ["Cheese",
        "Chickpea Dip",
        "Fish Sauce",
        "Vegetable"],
        "answer": 0
    }
    ]
}